IObit Driver Booster 12 Update History

V12.0 2024.09.12
+ Expanded database to support updating 15,000,000+ drivers for more devices
+ Supported more new hardware, including Intel Core Ultra, AMD Ryzen 9000 Series, and AMD Ryzen AI 300 Series
+ Latest drivers offered to boost gaming performance and system stability
+ Optimized the scan engine to accelerate scanning by up to 18%
+ Optimized the driver installation engine to increase installation speed by 7% and installation success rate by 25%
+ Improved Game Boost to boost gaming performance by up to 5%
+ Revamped the update program for faster update
+ New modern UI to make it more beautiful and easy-to-use
+ Supported 38 localized languages
+ More can be discovered by you

